Broadway is like the main thoroughfare
down the island of Manhattan.
Manhattan
and then running through the whole
island is this main street which is
Broadway.
This is a great book by the way.
My office sits like one story above
Broadway. There's always something going
on.
What's going on outside? I don't know.
You ask the
police. I'll go ask.
I'll I'll let you know. What's going on
out here? They're doing a demonstration
later. It's a May Day so they're they're
just clearing the block for all the
people that walk through later on. But
not like a fun parade like a
I don't know if it's fun.
>> [laughter]
>> All right. Take care.
>> All right. That's my office. If If you
need anything. You got it.
>> [music]
>> When I was He said it's a demonstration
and I was like like a parade like a fun
parade and he was like no I don't think
it's going to be fun. So it's probably
just a protest.
>> [music]
>> Thanks. We got a situation outside.
Could you hear the police?
I did. There is no parking on Broadway
today. You must park your car on the
side street. I thought it was you on the
on the loudspeaker.
>> No but I've been like on work phone
calls and every 2 minutes I like no one
can hear what I'm saying cuz it's so
loud.
What are you doing?
Why are you stepping on my my couch with
your shoes?
>> wanted to get a better
>> Take off your sneakers. No. What are you
doing?
It's my nice couch.
>> so sorry.
Put
>> [laughter]
>> your shoes on.
It's action packed day.
I slept 4 hours, woke up at 6, couldn't
go back to sleep, and came in here.
11:34 a.m. Reporting live from Broadway.
The police have cleared all the parking
off of Broadway. They've towed one BMW.
>> [music]
>> I I have no idea what's going on out.
Stay tuned. Stay tuned for updates.
How you doing?
What's up?
>> [music]
>> The amazing thing about street closures
is that
the road that's closed you get the whole
road to yourself but every other street
is just [music] gridlock traffic.
>> [music]
>> I almost
I almost died.
How you doing man?
I'm chilling.
Stay safe. I will. I'll do my best.
>> [music]
>> Long time ago.
What's going on here girls?
How's business?
>> [music]
>> It's been a while since we've done a
Billy update Candace. Give us a Billy
update.
>> That's very close.
Do you still want to quit?
I'm working on something very special
for you for Father's Day.
Did I tell you I'm going on a surfing
trip on Mother's Day?
No. Really? I put it on the calendar.
You didn't say it was a surfing trip.
What? It's not very nice. I know but
it's it's a
What are you going to do for me in
return?
This is not turning out as I hoped it
would turn out.
Can I show pictures of this stuff? No no
no no. Can I eat this? Yes.
It's about time I did this cuz I've been
really wanting to. I've been watching
the clock.
I'm watching the clock on this one.
Are you alluding to something new you're
making with?
>> Yes.
Are you Are you making a watch? Well I'm
not making it. Making [music] a watch
better.
You're making a Casio F-109 in custom
Billy? Yeah. Is this going to be gold?
It can be.
>> [music]
>> Come on. Tell me what happened.
She punched somebody. Yeah because
somebody pushed her in a bar and so she
punched him. I'm like where? And I
thought she'd say like you know on his
arm. In his face. In New York City you
punch someone in the face?
>> she did.
>> [laughter]
>> I had to. She had to.
A guy pushed her. All right. Remember
guys violence is never the answer.
>> [music]
[music]
[laughter]
>> You look handsome today. Really? Yeah. I
look I'm I'm even I'm even more handsome
though I have my I took my hat off. We
haven't had a proper lunch date in a
minute. For real?
All right. I got to get to work. Get to
work. Come by the office.
Got to. All right. Take care buddy.
Hey you're upstairs.
Does it look like whatever is coming
down Broadway is coming down Broadway?
I'm coming up. I'm coming up.
>> [music]
>> Jordan.
I locked my phone.
Locked in the stairwell.
Hey I was locked in the stairwell.
>> [music]
>> Ah look how clean Broadway is. I don't
know what it is. I tried to look at it
with the binoculars and I couldn't. The
King of England's in town so
I don't know if he
You got a charge boosted? Yeah.
I got an extra. Can we go see? Yeah
let's go.
Oh wait this is it.
Okay. These cops are the front of
Is this a protest? What is this for? Uh
May Day. It's like International
Workers' Day.
>> [music]
>> I've seen your
video stuff on the I appreciate it.
What does it look like from up there
Preston?
The view up here looks pretty good.
>> [music]
>> And just like that it's over. To
everyone that participated in the labor
march I hope you brought attention to
your cause and yeah I guess that's just
another Friday
in New York City.
>> [music]